

Frontend Developer Ha Noi, Vietnam

giahung197bg@gmail.com









## About

Hi, my name is Hung, i'm 26 years old. I got a bachelor of Electronics Telecommunication Engineering at Ha Noi University of Science and Technology. Besides, i am really passionate about Javascript and Web Development.

I am also an open-source enthusiast and maintainer. I love how collaboration and knowledge sharing happens through open-source and I am happy to see what I do could eventually feedback to the community and industry.

#### **Work Experience**

#### AgileTech Vietnam Frontend Developer

Dec 2020 - Present | Nhân Hòa, quận Thanh Xuân, Hà Nội

- Worked on developing and maintaining the projects of the company.
- Training new members of the company.

### Beau Agency Vietnam Frontend Developer Intern

Dec 2019 - Dec 2020 | Hoàng Văn Thái, Thanh Xuân, Hà Nội

- Worked on developing and maintaining the company's e-commerce, landing page website
- Developed and maintained the project on shopify platform.

### **Projects**

#### Hillridge <sup>↗</sup>

Agricultural construction insurance

#### Maby Salon <sup>对</sup>

Book an appointment, Manage an appointment, View details of the salon, Notification function when there is a new appointment, cancel an appointment

#### Summoners Arena 7

Building a website to buy and sell heroes with tokens, Exchange tokens, Create and manage events

#### Maby <sup>↗</sup>

Book an appointment, Search for the nearest salon, Search for a salon by city, View details of the salon, Notification function when there is a new appointment, cancel an appointment

#### Gourmet Market Thailand 7

Building a sales website, Manage orders, Order function, Order management, product review, Order payment by visa/mastercard

#### XO Sections 7

XO Sections is a great solution with tons of customizing options and easy-to-use interface.

## **Open Source Projects**

Svg To Font O 7

Convert svg to font

**\*** 2

Quillijs Resize Image O 7

A module resize image for quilljs

**★** 4

React Sticky O 7

A library sticky element for reactjs

**★** 6

More Projects...

CSS To Tailwindcss O 7

Convert css to tailwindcss

\* 4

CSV Parser ○ 7

A module parse csv file for nodejs

**★** 4

React OTP Input O ↗

A library otp input for reactjs

★7

# Stacks

Frontend TypeScript, JavaScript, Reactjs, Nextjs, Vite, Svelte

Backend Node, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Nginx, Docker

**DevOps** Firebase

Languages C/C++

### Education

**Electronics Telecommunication Engineering, Engineer**, Hanoi university of science and technology Sep 2015 - Sep 2020

## Languages

Vietnamese (Native speaker), English (Beginner)

Online Version

Last updated at August 29th 2023, 11:50:15 pm